Pro and cons.
Red Notice is a action, comedy, crime film directed by Rawson Marshall Thurber.
An Interpol-issued Red Notice is a global alert to hunt
and capture the world's most wanted.
But when a daring heist brings together the FBI's top profiler and two
rival criminals, there's no telling what will happen.
John Hartley, played by Dwayne Johnson.
Nolan Booth, played by Ryan Reynolds.
Sarah Black / The Bishop, played by Gal Gadot.
Inspector Urvashi Das, played by Ritu Arya.
Sotto Voce, played by Chris Diamantopoulos.
Tambwe, played by Ivan Mbakop.
Red Notice is a 2021 American action comedy film written and directed by Rawson Marshall
Thurber starring Dwayne Johnson alongside Ryan Reynolds, Gal Gadot, and Ritu Arya.
It marks the third collaboration between Thurber and Johnson,
following Central Intelligence (2016) and Skyscraper (2018).
In the film, an FBI agent reluctantly teams up with a renowned art
thief in order to catch an even more notorious thief.
Originally planned for release by Universal Pictures, the
film was acquired by Netflix for distribution.
It began a limited theatrical release on November 5, 2021, before
digitally streaming on the platform on November 12, 2021.
It was not very well received by critics for its plot and screenwriting, though the performances
(particularly Johnson and Reynolds), action sequences and humor were praised.
Netflix claims the film became the most-watched film in its debut weekend, as well as having been the
most-watched film on the platform until being surpassed by KPop Demon Hunters in 2025.
It also became the 5th most-streamed movie title of 2021.
Two sequels are in development and will be filmed back-to-back with
Johnson, Reynolds, Gadot, and Thurber expected to return.
The film explores themes of fbi, interpol, cleopatra, heist, art thief.
The tone is lighthearted.